Guide to the Virginia Nelson playbills collection, 1939-2007
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections Research Center, George Mason University
Virginia Nelson playbills collection
1939-2007
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
Virginia Nelson
C0015
6 linear feet (12 boxes)
This collection contains playbills for performances at a variety of venues in the Washington D.C. metro area, including the National Theatre, Arena Stage, the New Gayety Theatre, the Warner Theatre, and the John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, as well as multiple smaller, local theatres and companies, and others across the United States and internationally.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Collection donated by Virginia Nelson in 2007.
Historical Information
Following World War II, Washington, D.C. gradually acquired a vibrant theatre and performing arts scene, due in large part to the population growth as the federal government expanded. In particular the opening of John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts in the early 1970s signaled the great importance of performing arts for the citizens of the Washington, D.C. metro area.
Scope and Content
The Virginia Nelson playbills collection represents the rise and expansion of theatre and the performing arts in the Metro D.C. area, including a variety of performances at a multitude of venues over the course of eight decades, beginning in the 1930s and ending in the early 2000s. From plays and musical theatre, to opera, ballet, and musical acts, the gamut of the performing arts is represented within the collection. This collection contains playbills for performances at a variety of D.C. area venues, including the National Theatre, Arena Stage, the New Gayety Theatre, the Warner Theatre, Wolf Trap, Signature Theatre, and the John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, as well as other theatres across the nation and abroad, including those from Broadway in New York and the West End in London. Many of the playbills come from renowned "classic" performances of certain works, many starring famous actors. Also represented in the collection are smaller, local theatrical venues, companies, and performances. Note: Included in the collection were a number of Arena Stage Playbills, which were removed except for one that was not already included in the Arena Stage records. All other Arena Stage playbills (before the 2006/2007 season) are available in the
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collections Research Center also holds many other.
Index Terms
Geographical Names:
New York (City); London, England.; United States.; Washington (D.C.)
Corporate Names:
Arena Stage (Organization: Washington, D.C.); John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts (U.S.); National Theatre (Washington, D.C.); New Gayety Theatre (Organization: Washington, D.C.); Warner Theatre (Washington, D.C.); Wolf Trap National Park for the Performing Arts (Va.)
Subjects:
Ballet.; Musical theater; Musical theater--England--London.; Musical theater--New York (State)--New York.; Musical theater--Washington (D.C.); Opera.; Performing arts.; Plays.; Theater--Washington (D.C.); Theater--New York (State)
Contents List
  - National Theatre - "Set to Music,", January 9, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - National Theatre - "Du Barry Was A Lady,", November 1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Roadside Theatre - "The Frog,", July 22, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Willard Hotel Roof - "Bertha, The Sewing Machine Girl,", 1941 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cross Roads Theatre - "The Male Animal,", 1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - National Theatre "The Cream in the Well,", January 14, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - National Theatre - "Claudia,", January 27, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Longacre Theatre - "Johnny Belinda,", February 16, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - National Theatre - "Tobacco Road,", February 17, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - National Theatre - "The Little Foxes," Featuring Tallulah Bankhead, March 17, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Catholic University of America - "Cook Book,", April 23, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - National Theatre - "The Student Prince,", May 5, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cross Roads Theatre - "Private Lives,", July 1941 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The St. Paul's Players - "Tish,", October 15, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - National Theatre - "Faust,", February 6, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - National Theatre - "Louisiana Purchase,", February 23, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - The Winter Garden - "Sons O' Fun,", April 12, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Hollywood Theatre - "Banjo Eyes,", April 12, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - National Theatre - "Punch and Julia,", May 4, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - The Catholic University of America - "Count Me In!,", May 10, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - National Theatre - "Franklin Street,", September 21, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - National Theatre - "The Pirate,", October 12, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - National Theatre - "The Doughgirls,", December 7, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Broadhurst Theatre - "Show Time,", 1943 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The Booth Theatre - "Blithe Spirit,", January 31, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - National Theatre - "Junior Miss,", February 8, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - National Theatre - "Priorities of 1942," Featuring Gloria Swanson, March 1, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - National Theatre - "Blossom Time,", April 12, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - The Catholic University of America - "Eddie the First,", May 5, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - National Theatre - "Dracula," Featuring Bela Lugosi, June 21, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - National Theatre - "Arsenic and Old Lace," Featuring Boris Karloff, August 30, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - National Theatre - "Big Time,", September 20, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - National Theatre - "Oklahoma,", October 18, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - The Broadhurst Theatre - "Early to Bed,", November 14, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The Winter Garden - "Ziegfeld Follies,", November 14, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - National Symphony Orchestra - Ballet Theatre, November 14, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - The Washington Grand Opera Association - "Cavalleria Rusticana" and "I Pagliacci,", December 21, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - National Theatre - "Over Twenty One," Featuring Ruth Gordon, December 27, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - National Theatre - "Marianne,", January 10, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - National Theatre - "Kiss and Tell,", January 17, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - National Theatre - "The Corn is Green," Featuring Ethel Barrymore, April 17, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - The Cape Theatre - "The Philadelphia Story,", June 20, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - National Theatre - "Wallflower,", August 28, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - National Theatre - "Our Fanny," Featuring Joy Hodges, September 18, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - The Catholic University of America - "The Life and Death of Tom Thumb the Great,", January 14, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - National Theatre - "The Merry Widow,", January 29, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - National Theatre - "Catherine Was Great," Featuring Mae West, February 19, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - The Washington Grand Opera Company - "Carmen,", March 15, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - The Music Box - "Star and Garter,' Featuring Gypsy Rose Lee, June 13, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - National Theatre - "Leonide Massine's Ballet Russe Highlights,", July 18, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - National Theatre - "Good Night Ladies,", July 23, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - National Theatre - "Life with Father,", August 6, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - National Symphony Orchestra - Ballet Theatre, November 11, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - National Theatre - "The Late George Apley,", November 19, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Constitution Hall - "Gladys Swarthout,", November 18, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - National Theatre - "Spring in Brazil,", November 27, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Cross Roads Theatre - "The Pursuit of Happiness,", 1946 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Cross Roads Theatre - "George and Margaret", 1946 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - National Theatre - "Up in Central Park,", January 6, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - National Theatre - "O Mistress Mine,", January 7, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - National Theatre - "The Hasty Heart,", February 4, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - National Theatre - "He Who Gets Slapped," Featuring Dennis King, March 4, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - National Theatre - "Miss Jones" by Ruth Gordon, Mach 18, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Benefit - Mayflower Hotel - "Mission to Matthew,", March 18, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - National Theatre - "Blossom Time,", April 1, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - National Theatre - "Hamlet," Featuring Maurice Evans, April 15, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - National Theatre - "The Two Mrs. Carrolls,", April 22, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - National Theatre - "The Merry Wives of Windsor,", May 6, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - National Theatre - "Laura,", May 27, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - National Theatre - "The Voice of the Turtle,", June 17, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Olney Theatre - "Private Lives,", September 10, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - The Forty-Sixth Street Theatre - "The Red Mill,", September 16, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - National Theatre - "Come On Up," Featuring Mae West, September 23, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Majestic Theatre - "Carousel,", September 23, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - National Theatre - "Pygmalion," Featuring Gertrude Lawrence, October 21, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Lisner Auditorium - "Joan of Lorainne," Featuring Ingrid Bergman and Sam Wanamaker, October 29, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - National Theatre - "Apple of His Eye,", November 4, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Little Theatre - "Henry V," Featuring Laurence Olivier, November 7, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - National Theatre - "The Glass Menagerie,", February 10, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - National Theatre - "State of the Union,", March 3, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - National Theatre - "The Fatal Weakness," Featuring Ina Claire, March 10, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - National Treasure - "The Iceman Cometh,", April 7, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - National Treasure - "Love for Love," Featuring John Gielgud, May 13, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - National Theatre - "Lute Song," Featuring Yul Brynner and Dolly Haas, May 26, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - National Theatre - "I Remember Mama,", December 27, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - National Theatre - "Harvey," Featuring Frank Fay, June 21, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Olney Theatre - "Too Many Husbands,", July 8, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Catholic University of America - "Arms and the Man,", July 11, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Olney Theatre - "Up To Now,", July 19, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - San Carlo Opera Company - "Aida,", circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - San Carlo Opera Company - "An American Institution,", circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - National Theatre - "Antigone,", circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Olney Theatre - "Biography,", circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - New Gayety Theatre - "Brigadoon,", circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Willard Hotel Roof - "Broken HeArts of Broadway,", circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Constitution Hall - "Gay Nineties,", circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Cross Roads Theatre - "Mr. Barry's Etchings,", circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Grand Opera Libretto - "Pagliacci,", circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Olney Theatre - "Skylark,", circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Cross Roads Theatre - "Spider Island,", circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - San Carlo Opera Company - "The Chocolate Soldier,", circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Olney Theatre - "The Curtain Rises,", circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Sam H. Harris - "The Man Who Came to Dinner,", circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - The Antigone of Sophocles - Translation by Lewis Campbell, circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - New Gayety Theatre - "Born Yesterday," Featuring Judy Holliday, November 20, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - New Gayety Theatre - "Come Back, Little Sheba,", January 15, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - New Gayety Theatre - "The Autumn Garden," Featuring Florence Eldrige and Frederic March, February 11, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - New Gayety Theatre - "The Cocktail Party", March 31, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - National Theatre - "Call Me Madam," Featuring Ethel Merman, May 5, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - National Theatre - "Gentlemen Prefer Blondes," Featuring Carol Channing, June 2, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Henry Miller's Theatre - "The Moon is Blue,", October 27, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 46th Street Theatre - "Guys and Dolls,", November 3, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - National Theatre - "Top Banana," Featuring Phil Silvers, November 10, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Sam S. Shubert Theater - "Horses in Midstream,", March 17, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Sam S. Shubert Theater - "Pal Joey,", April 20, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Sam S. Shubert Theater - "Jose Greco,", September 29, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Sam S. Shubert Theater - "My 3 Angels,", March 1, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Constitution Hall - Liberace, September 26, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Theater de Lys - "The Threepenny Opera,", 1955 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Martin Beck Theatre - "The Teahouse of the August Moon," Featuring Eli Wallach, July 14, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - National Theatre - "The Vamp," Featuring Carol Channing, October 31, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - National Theatre - "Janus," Featuring Robert Preston, November 14, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Sam S. Shubert Theater - "Kismet,", January 23, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - National Theatre - "Damn Yankees,", February 13, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Sam S. Shubert Theater - "Bus Stop,", February 20, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - National Theatre - "Li'l Abner,", September 17, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - National Theatre - "Cat Hot On A Hot Tin Roof,", November 19, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - National Theatre - "Inherit the Wind," Featuring Melvyn Douglas, December 31, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - National Theatre - "Ziegfeld Follies,", February 12, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - National Theatre - "West Side Story,", August 26, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - National Theatre - "Separate Tables," Featuring Geraldine Page, October 28, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - National Theatre - "Middle of The Night," Featuring Edward G. Robinson, December 30, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Ontario Theatre - The Bolshoi Ballet - "Giselle,", January 1958 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - National Theatre - "Interlock," Featuring Celeste Holm, Maximilian Schell, and Rosemary Harris, January 27, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Constitution Hall - Mantovani and His New Music, February 1, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Sam S. Shubert Theater - "Much Ado About Nothing," Featuring Katharine Hepburn, February 10, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Sam S. Shubert Theater - "Visit To A Small Planet," Featuring Cyril Ritchard, February 24, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - National Theatre - "Auntie Mame,", March 3, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - National Theatre - American Ballet Theatre, March 10, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - National Theatre - "Long Day's Journey Into Night,", March 17, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - National Theatre - "No Time For Sergeants,", March 24, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Constitution Hall - An Evening with Bennett Cerf, May 2, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - National Theatre - "The Diary of Anne Frank,", June 9, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Lowe's Capitol Theatre - Moiseyev Dance Company from Moscow, June 16, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - National Theatre - "Look Back in Anger,", December 22, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - National Theatre - "Redhead," Featuring Gwen Verdon and Richard Kiley, December 30, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - National Theatre - "Bells Are Ringing," Featuring Judy Holliday, April 6, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - National Theatre - "Sunrise At Campobello,", June 29, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - National Theatre - "A Loss of Roses," Featuring Shirley Booth, November 2, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - National Theatre - "The Pleasure of His Company," Featuring Cyril Ritchard, December 7, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - National Theatre - "Dear Liar,", December 28, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - London Films - "Tales of Hoffman," Featuring Moira Shearer, circa 1950s (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Versailles - "Nice To See You,", circa 1950s (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Carter Barron Ampitheater - "Belafonte" - Harry Belafonte, circa June 1950 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Little Theatre of Alexandria - "The Recruiting Officer,", circa 1950s (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - The Broadway Theatre - "Gypsy," Featuring Ethel Merman, January 1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - National Theatre - "The World of Suzie Wong,", January 11, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - National Theatre - "The Good Soup," Featuring Ruth Gordon, February 15, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - National Theatre - "One More River,", February 29, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - National Theatre - "Look Homeward Angel,", March 14, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Dock Street Theatre - "Hiddydoddy,", March 24, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - National Theatre - "The Dark At The Top of the Stairs," Featuring Joan Blondell, April 11, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - National Theatre - "Sweet Bird of Youth," Featuring Geraldine Page and Rip Torn, May 9, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - National Theatre - "My Fair Lady,", June 27, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Carter Barron Amphitheatre - Jimmy Durante, July 1960 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - National Theatre - "Irma La Douce,", September 19, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - National Theatre - "Duel of Angels,", October 10, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - The Discount Record Shop - An Evening with Mort Sahl and the Limelighters, October 14, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Constitution Hall - Eileen Farrell, October 30, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - National Theatre - "The Andersonville Trial,", December 26, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Sam S. Shubert Theater - "Bye Bye Birdie," Featuring Chita Rivera and Dick Van Dyke, January 16, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - National Theatre - "Carnival!" Featuring Jerry Orbach, March 20, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - National Theatre - "Becket," Featuring Laurence Olivier and Arthur Kennedy, April 10, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - National Theatre - "The Music Man," Featuring Forrest Tucker, July 3, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - National Theatre - "A Taste of Honey,", September 18, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - National Theatre - "Toys in the Attic,", October 16, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - National Theatre - "Sunday in New York," Featuring Robert Redford, November 6, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - National Theatre - "The Best Man,", January 1, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - National Theatre - "Fiorello!,", January 8, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - National Theatre - "La Plume de Ma Tante,", March 26, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - National Theatre - "Come Blow Your Horn,", July 30, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - National Theatre - "Mr. President,", October 1962 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - National Theatre - "Natural Affection,", January 21, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - National Theatre - "Hot Spot," Featuring Judy Holliday, February 4, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - National Theatre - "Mary, Mary,", March 25, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - National Theatre - "Milk and Honey,", May 6, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - National Theatre - "Take Her, She's Mine," Featuring Tom Ewell, June 3, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - National Theatre - "The Sound of Music,", July 1, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - National Theatre - "Here's Love,", August 26, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - National Theatre - "A Thousand Clowns," Featuring Dane Clark and Margaret O'Brien, September 16, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - National Theatre - "Seidman and Son," Featuring Sam Levene, November 18, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - National Theatre - "Barefoot In The Park," Featuring Robert Redford, September 30, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - National Theatre - "Hello Dolly!" Featuring Carol Channing, December 23, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - National Theatre - "Never Too Late,", February 1964 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - National Theatre - "Josephine Baker and Her Company,", March 1964 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - National Theatre - "Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?,", May 1964 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - National Theatre - "I Was Dancing," Featuring Burgess Meredith, October 1964 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - National Theatre - "Zizi," Featuring Zizi Jeanmaire, October 1964 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Constitution Hall - National Symphony, November 10, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - National Theatre - "Alfie!" Featuring Terence Stamp, November 1964 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - National Theatre - "After The Fall,", November 1964 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Winter Garden - "Funny Girl," Featuring Barbra Streisand, December 1964 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - National Theatre - "110 In The Shade,", December 1964 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - National Theatre - "Any Wednesday,", January 1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - National Theatre - "The Roar of the Greasepaint - The Smell of the Crowd," Featuring Cyril Ritchard, February 1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - National Theatre - "Diamond Orchid,", February 1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - National Theatre - "The Odd Couple," Featuring Walter Mathau, February 1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - National Theatre - "How To Succeed In Business Without Really Trying,", April 1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - National Theatre - "Pickwick,", September 195 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - National Theatre - "Cactus Flower," Featuring Lauren Bacall, November 1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Constitution Hall - Washington National Sympathy, November 27, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - National Theatre - "The Wayward Stork,", January 1966 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - National Theatre - "Luv,", January 1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - National Theatre - "Hostile Witness,", February 1966 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Constitution Hall - New York Philharmonic, February 21, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - National Theatre - "The Subject Was Roses," Featuring Martin Sheen, March 1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - National Theatre - "The Owl and the Pussycat," Featuring Eartha Kitt, March 1966 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - National Theatre - "I Do! I Do!" Featuring Mary Martin and Robert Preston, October 1966 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Winter Garden Theatre - "Mame," Featuring Angela Lansbury and Bea Arthur, December 1966 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - The Palace Theatre - "Sweet Charity," Featuring Gwen Verdon, December 1966 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - National Theatre - "Man of La Mancha,", February 1967 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - National Theatre - Eddie Fisher and Buddy Hackett, June 1967 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - National Theatre - "Wait A Minim!,", August 1967 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - National Theatre - "Mata Hari,", November 1967 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Washington Performing Arts Society - Mantovani and His Concert Orchestra, November 26, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - The Private Arts Foundation - An Evening with Edward Villella, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - National Theatre - "The Killing of Sister George,", January 1968 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - National Theatre - "Fiddler On The Roof," Featuring Paul Lipson, August 1968 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Bethesda-Chevy Chase High School - "On A Clear Day You Can See Forever,", 1960s (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Lowe's Capitol Theatre - Leningrad Kirov Ballet, circa 1960s (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Circle In The Square at Ford's Theatre - "Max Morath At The Turn of the Century,", January 1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Shady Grove Music Fair - "W.C." Featuring Mickey Rooney and Bernadette Peters, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - George Washington University - Sponsored - National Ballet, January 8, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Kennedy Center Concert Hall - New Orleans Jazz and Ragtime Festival, November 7, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Olney Theatre - "Tartuffe,", July 11, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 32)